A Guide to the Winthrop Rockefeller Foundation records FA248
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Grants, 1972-2001; 2 (Reel 15, Frame 203)
  - Programs, 1976-2001; 1 (Reel 15, Frame 204)
    - Pulaski County Special School District, Sylvan Hills High School, 89-17, 1989-1990 (Reel 81, Frame 784)
    - Pulaski County Special School District, Jacksonville Junior High School, 89-96, 1989 (Reel 81, Frame 801)
    - Pulaski County Special School District, Bates Elementary School, 89-111, 1989-1990 (Reel 81, Frame 815)
    - Pulaski County Special School District, Teachers of Tomorrow, 89-114, 1989-1990 (Reel 81, Frame 829)
    - Pulaski County Special School District, Project YES (Youth Experiencing Success), Original Proposal-Grant Agreement, 1990-1992 (Reel 81, Frame 848)
      Grant number: 90-60
    - Pulaski County Special School District, Project YES (Youth Experiencing Success), 90-60, Year One-Year Two, 1990-1992 (Reel 81, Frame 958)
    - Pulaski County Special School District, 90-119, 1990-1999 (Reel 81, Frame 1225)
    - Pulaski County Special School District, Jacksonville Elementary School, 91-39, 1991-1992 (Reel 82, Frame 1)
    - Pulaski County Special School District, Robinson Elementary School, 91-120, 1991-1992 (Reel 82, Frame 83)
    - Pulaski County Special School District, Scott Elementary School, 92-117, 1992-1993 (Reel 82, Frame 125)
    - Pulaski County Special School District, Sylvan Hills Junior High School, 92-119, 1992-1993 (Reel 82, Frame 155)
    - Pulaski County Special School District, 93-130, 1993-1994 (Reel 82, Frame 207)
    - Pulaski County Special School District, Tri-Level Early Intervention Project, 94-90, 1994-1997 (Reel 82, Frame 245)
    - Pulaski County Special School District, 95-129, 1995-1996 (Reel 82, Frame 416)
    - Pulaski County Special School District, 95-157, 1995-1996 (Reel 82, Frame 646)
    - Pulaski County Special School District, 95-159, 1995 (Reel 82, Frame 505)
    - Pulaski Heights Presbyterian Church, Home Grown Markets, Incorporated, 84-395, 1984-1985 (Reel 82, Frame 548)
    - Pulaski Heights Presbyterian Church, 85-482, 1985-1986 (Reel 82, Frame 582)
    - Pulaski Heights Presbyterian Church, Agricultural Marketing Project of Arkansas, 85-498, 1985-1986 (Reel 82, Frame 612)
    - Pulaski Metropolitan Initiative, Incorporated, 94-108, 1994-1998 (Reel 82, Frame 641)
    - Pulaski Metropolitan Initiative, Incorporated, 95-166, 1995-1999 (Reel 82, Frame 875)
    - Quapaw Quarter Association, Incorporated, 95-178, 1995-2000 (Reel 83, Frame 1)
    - RAIN Arkansas, Incorporated, Regional AIDS Interfaith Network of Arkansas, 92-115, Original Proposal-Year One, 1992-1994 (Reel 83, Frame 269)
    - RAIN Arkansas, Incorporated, Regional AIDS Interfaith Network of Arkansas, 92-115, Year Two-Year Three, 1993-1995 (Reel 83, Frame 480)
    - Ray Scott Associates, Professional Services Agreement, 1995 (Reel 83, Frame 740)
    - Ray, Victor K., Professional Services Agreement, 1988-1990 (Reel 83, Frame 768)
    - Reading is Fundamental, Incorporated, 1991 Payout, 90-36, 1989-1991 (Reel 83, Frame 851)
    - Regenerative Agriculture Association, 86-688, 1986-1988 (Reel 83, Frame 1089)
    - Research and Development of Environmentally Safe Agriculture Insecticides and Related Products, Incorporated, @1-92-144, 1991-1993 (Reel 84, Frame 1)
    - Resource Development Council, Professional Services Agreement, 1981 (Reel 84, Frame 208)
    - Resource Policy Center, Thayer School of Engineering, Dartmouth College, Resource Inventory, 82-270, 1982-1983 (Reel 84, Frame 322)
    - Rison Public Schools, 92-21, 1992 (Reel 84, Frame 367)
    - Rodale Institute, 87-770, 1987-1988 (Reel 84, Frame 412)
    - Rogers Public Schools, 88-25, 1988-1989 (Reel 84, Frame 433)
    - Rogers Public Schools, 88-162, 1988-1989 (Reel 84, Frame 450)
    - Rogers Public Schools, Elmwood Junior High School, 89-78, 1989-1990 (Reel 84, Frame 468)
    - Rogers Public Schools, 91-13, 1991-1992 (Reel 84, Frame 489)
    - Rural Special Schools, 87-740, 1987 (Reel 84, Frame 589)
    - Russellville Public Schools, 85-563, 1985-1987 (Reel 84, Frame 606)
    - Russellville Public Schools, 86-666, 1986-1987 (Reel 84, Frame 633)
    - Russellville Public Schools, 87-852, 1987-1988 (Reel 84, Frame 653)
    - Russellville Public Schools, 88-117, 1988-1989 (Reel 84, Frame 673)
    - Russellville Public Schools, Center Valley Elementary School, 89-76, 1989-1990 (Reel 84, Frame 692)
    - Russellville Public Schools, 89-123, 1989-1990 (Reel 84, Frame 708)
    - Russellville Public Schools, 90-85, 1990-1991 (Reel 84, Frame 729)
    - Russellville Public Schools, 93-143, 1993-1996 (Reel 84, Frame 779)
    - Russellville Public Schools, 95-62, 1995-1996 (Reel 84, Frame 977)
    - Russellville Public Schools, 95-70, 1995-1996 (Reel 84, Frame 1025)
    - Sandflat-Glendale Neighborhood Development Corporation, 89-116, 1989-1991 (Reel 84, Frame 1082)
    - Sandflat-Glendale Neighborhood Development Corporation, 92-132, 1992-1993 (Reel 84, Frame 1099)
    - Sandflat-Glendale Neighborhood Development Corporation, 93-234, 1993-1998 (Reel 85, Frame 1)
    - Sanctuary, Incorporated, 92-135, 1992-1993 (Reel 85, Frame 221)
    - Sanctuary, Incorporated, 93-233, 1993-1995 (Reel 85, Frame 270)
    - Saratoga Schools, 93-115, 1993-1994 (Reel 85, Frame 310)
    - Save the Children, Incorporated, Arkansas Delta Project, 78-1006, 1978-1979 (Reel 85, Frame 343)
    - Save the Children, Incorporated, Arkansas Delta Project, 79-1011, 1979-1980 (Reel 85, Frame 354)
    - Save the Children, Incorporated, Arkansas Delta Project, 80-1006, 1980-1981 (Reel 85, Frame 370)
    - Save the Children, Incorporated, Arkansas Delta Project, Livestock Needs Assessment, 82-302, 1982 (Reel 85, Frame 402)
    - Save the Children, Incorporated, 88-55, 1988-1992 (Reel 85, Frame 417)
    - SCAN Volunteer Services, Incorporated, Suspect Child Abuse and Neglect, 94-95, Original Proposal, 1994-1996 (Reel 85, Frame 466)
    - SCAN Volunteer Services, Incorporated, Suspect Child Abuse and Neglect, Grant Agreement-Year Three, 1994-1998 (Reel 85, Frame 798)
      Grant number: 94-95
    - Schriver, Joe M., Professional Services Agreement, 1987 (Reel 85, Frame 1002)
    - S.C.O.R.E., Service Corps of Retired Executives, 84-421, 1984-1985 (Reel 85, Frame 1007)
    - Scotland School District, 95-151, 1995-1996 (Reel 85, Frame 1022)
    - Searcy County Airport Commission, 89-108, 1989-1990 (Reel 85, Frame 1063)
    - Searcy County Airport Commission, 90-103, Original Proposal-Year One, 1990-1992 (Reel 85, Frame 1086)
    - Searcy County Airport Commission, 90-103, Year Two-Year Three, 1991-1993 (Reel 86, Frame 1)
    - Searcy County Airport Commission, 93-229, 1993-1997 (Reel 86, Frame 157)
    - Searcy Public Schools, 88-9, 1988-1989 (Reel 86, Frame 276)
    - Searcy Public Schools, 93-13, 1992-1993 (Reel 86, Frame 291)
    - Second Genesis Ministries, Incorporated, 91-106, 1991-1992 (Reel 86, Frame 353)
    - Second Genesis Ministries, Incorporated, 92-204, 1992-1993 (Reel 86, Frame 423)
    - Second Genesis Ministries, Incorporated, 94-93, 1994-1999 (Reel 86, Frame 472)
    - SEED, Incorporated, Social, Economic and Educational Development, 92-44, 1992-1994 (Reel 86, Frame 776)
    - SEED, Incorporated, Social, Economic and Educational Development, 94-153, 1994-1995 (Reel 86, Frame 830)
    - Shelby, Linda, Professional Services Agreement, 1987 (Reel 86, Frame 889)
    - The Shepard's Ranch, Incorporated, 95-92, Original Proposal-Year One, 1994-1997 (Reel 86, Frame 894)
    - The Shepard's Ranch, Incorporated, 95-92, Year Two-Year Three, 1996-1998 (Reel 86, Frame 1047)
    - Sheridan School District, 85-500, 1985-1986 (Reel 87, Frame 1)
    - Sheridan School District, 86-687, 1986-1987 (Reel 87, Frame 33)
    - Sheridan School District, Expansion, 86-692, 1986-1988 (Reel 87, Frame 61)
    - Sheridan School District, 87-813, 1987-1988 (Reel 87, Frame 95)
    - Sheridan School District, 88-122, 1988-1990 (Reel 87, Frame 118)
    - Sheridan School District, Reconstructing, 89-82, 1989-1990 (Reel 87, Frame 151)
    - Sheridan School District, East End Elementary School, 90-70, 1990-1991 (Reel 87, Frame 180)
    - Sheridan School District, Sheridan Junior High School, 91-134, 1991 (Reel 87, Frame 289)
    - Sheridan School District, 93-8, 1993 (Reel 87, Frame 318)
    - Sheridan School District, 93-184, 1993-1994 (Reel 87, Frame 403)
    - Shirley Community Service and Development Corporation, 89-64, 1989-1990 (Reel 87, Frame 459)
    - Shirley Community Service and Development Corporation, 90-132, 1990-1993 (Reel 87, Frame 483)
    - Shirley Community Service and Development Corporation, 93-82, Original Proposal-Year One, 1993-1996 (Reel 87, Frame 667)
    - Shirley Community Service and Development Corporation, 93-82, Year Two-Year Four, 1995-1998 (Reel 88, Frame 1)
    - Shirley Public Schools, School Improvement, 94-22, 1993-1994 (Reel 88, Frame 328)
    - Shorter College, 93-230, 1993-1995 (Reel 88, Frame 379)
    - Siloam Springs Public Schools, Siloam Springs High School, 89-46, 1989-1990 (Reel 88, Frame 444)
    - Siloam Springs Public Schools, Southside Elementary School, 90-10, 1990 (Reel 88, Frame 464)
    - Siloam Springs Public Schools, 91-69, 1991 (Reel 88, Frame 519)
    - Siloam Springs Public Schools, 92-56, 1992 (Reel 88, Frame 567)
    - Siloam Springs Public Schools, 93-117, 1993-1994 (Reel 88, Frame 599)
    - Siloam Springs Public Schools, 93-219, 1993-1995 (Reel 88, Frame 750)
    - Sims, Opal, Professional Services Agreement, 1990 (Reel 88, Frame 692)
    - Skipping Rock Studios, Professional Services Agreement, 1990 (Reel 88, Frame 696)
    - Sloan-Hendrix School District, 92-96, 1992-1993 (Reel 88, Frame 701)
    - Solutions, Incorporated, An Arkansas Foundation Against Hunger and Homelessness, 89-91, 1989-1990 (Reel 88, Frame 882)
    - South Central Arkansas Community Action Authority, Professional Services Agreement, 1994 (Reel 88, Frame 917)
    - South Central Service Cooperative, 94-86, 1994-1995 (Reel 88, Frame 956)
    - South Central Service Cooperative, 95-106, 1995-1996 (Reel 88, Frame 991)
    - South Conway County School District, 87-801, 1987-1988 (Reel 88, Frame 1050)
    - South Conway County School District, 94-50, 1993-1994 (Reel 88, Frame 1068)
    - South Conway County School District, 95-24, 1995 (Reel 88, Frame 1115)
    - South Little Rock Community Development Corporation, 96-75, 1996-1998 (Reel 88, Frame 1144)
    - South Mississippi County School District, 95-156, 1995-1996 (Reel 88, Frame 1210)
    - Southeast Arkansas Community Action Corporation, 91-135, 1991-1993 (Reel 89, Frame 1)
    - Southeast Arkansas Community Development Corporation, 91-79, 1991-1993 (Reel 89, Frame 101)
    - Southeast Arkansas Community Development Corporation, 92-188, Original Proposal, 1992-1995 (Reel 89, Frame 213)
    - Southeast Arkansas Community Development Corporation, Grant Agreement-Year Three, 1992-1996 (Reel 89, Frame 420)
      Grant number: 92-188
    - Southeast Arkansas Educational Cooperative, 81-248, 1981-1982 (Reel 89, Frame 650)
    - Southeast Arkansas Educational Cooperative, 82-299, 1982-1983 (Reel 89, Frame 670)
    - Southeast Arkansas Educational Cooperative, 83-369, 1983-1984 (Reel 89, Frame 687)
    - Southeast Arkansas Educational Cooperative, 90-9, 1989-1991 (Reel 89, Frame 709)
    - Southeast Arkansas Educational Service Cooperative, 92-40, 1992-1993 (Reel 89, Frame 754)
    - Southern Arkansas University, Mentor Directory, 78-1018, 1978-1979 (Reel 89, Frame 800)
    - Southern Arkansas University, 83-393, 1983-1984 (Reel 89, Frame 816)
    - Southern Arkansas University, 84-424, 1984-1985 (Reel 89, Frame 831)
    - Southern Arkansas University, 85-533, 1985-1987 (Reel 89, Frame 859)
    - Southern Arkansas University, Small Farm and Technical Assistance, 86-690, 1986-1987 (Reel 89, Frame 888)
    - Southern Arkansas University, 87-826, 1987-1988 (Reel 89, Frame 918)
    - Southern Arkansas University, 90-101, 1990-1992 (Reel 89, Frame 938)
    - The Southern Center for International Studies, 93-39, 1992-1993 (Reel 90, Frame 1)
    - Southern Coalition for Educational Equity, Incorporated, 83-337, 1983-1984 (Reel 90, Frame 170)
    - Southern Coalition for Educational Equity, Incorporated, 84-420, 1984-1985 (Reel 90, Frame 206)
    - Southern Development Center, Professional Services Agreement, 1995 (Reel 90, Frame 231)
    - Southern Education Foundation, Incorporated, 88-35, 1988-1992 (Reel 90, Frame 239)
    - Southern Growth Policies Board, 89-99, 1989-1991 (Reel 90, Frame 309)
    - Southern Regional Council, 95-144, 1995-1998 (Reel 90, Frame 393)
    - Southside School District-Batesville, Southside Elementary School, 93-22, 1993 (Reel 90, Frame 403)
    - Southside School District-Batesville, Southside Middle School, 93-176, 1993-1994 (Reel 90, Frame 439)
    - Southwest Arkansas Community Development Corporation, 90-124, 1990-1991 (Reel 90, Frame 475)
    - Southwest Arkansas Community Development Corporation, 91-113, 1991-1993 (Reel 90, Frame 537)
    - Southwest Arkansas Community Development Corporation, 92-189, 1992-1996 (Reel 90, Frame 593)
    - Southwest Arkansas Community Development Corporation, 92-201, 1992-1994 (Reel 90, Frame 797)
    - Southwest Arkansas Educational Cooperative, 81-249, 1981-1982 (Reel 90, Frame 826)
    - Southwest Arkansas Educational Cooperative, 82-300, 1982 (Reel 90, Frame 841)
    - Southwest Arkansas Educational Cooperative, 83-364, 1983-1984 (Reel 90, Frame 858)
    - Spa Area Independent Living Services, SAILS, 92-134, 1992-1993 (Reel 90, Frame 879)
    - Sparkman Public Schools, 85-537, 1985-1986 (Reel 90, Frame 930)
    - The Special Learning Center, 79-1023, 1979-1980 (Reel 90, Frame 956)
    - Springdale Public Schools, 86-574, 1986-1987 (Reel 90, Frame 993)
    - Springdale Public Schools, 86-581, 1986-1987 (Reel 90, Frame 1034)
    - Springdale Public Schools, 87-758, 1987-1988 (Reel 90, Frame 1059)
    - Springdale Public Schools, 88-40, 1988-1989 (Reel 90, Frame 1080)
    - Springdale Public Schools, 90-120, 1990-1991 (Reel 90, Frame 1104)
    - Springdale Public Schools, 91-30, 1991-1992 (Reel 90, Frame 1142)
    - Springdale Public Schools, Elmdale Elementary School, 91-118, 1991-1992 (Reel 90, Frame 1189)
    - Springdale Public Schools, Walker Elementary School, 92-73, 1992 (Reel 90, Frame 1223)
    - Springdale Public Schools, 93-120, 1993-1994 (Reel 91, Frame 1)
    - Springdale Public Schools, 93-129, 1993-1994 (Reel 91, Frame 42)
    - Springdale Public Schools, School Improvement, 93-205, 1993-1995 (Reel 91, Frame 74)
    - Springdale Public Schools, 95-12, 1995 (Reel 91, Frame 187)
    - St. Luke's AME Church, 84-433, 1984-1986 (Reel 91, Frame 226)
    - St. Michael's Catholic School, 92-78, 1992-1993 (Reel 91, Frame 250)
    - Star City Public Schools, 92-102, 1992-1993 (Reel 91, Frame 302)
    - Star City Public Schools, Jimmy Brown Elementary School, 92-116, 1992-1993 (Reel 91, Frame 365)
    - Star City Public Schools, 95-120, 1995 (Reel 91, Frame 400)
    - State of Arkansas, The Commission for Arkansas' Future, 90-69, 1990-1992 (Reel 91, Frame 425)
    - State of Arkansas, Department of Energy, i.e. Associates, Incorporated, Methanogenesis Project, 80-132, 1980-1981 (Reel 91, Frame 542)
    - State of Arkansas, Department of Local Services, 78-1000, 1978 (Reel 91, Frame 563)
    - Stephens Consulting, Incorporated, Professional Services Agreement, 1995-1996 (Reel 91, Frame 573)
    - Stewart, Andrea, Professional Services Agreement, 1988-1995 (Reel 91, Frame 583)
    - Stewart, H. D., Professional Services Agreement, 1985 (Reel 91, Frame 604)
    - Stewart, Jo Ann, Professional Services Agreement, 1985 (Reel 91, Frame 612)
    - Stuttgart Public Schools, 87-694, 1987 (Reel 91, Frame 624)
    - Stuttgart Public Schools, Stuttgart Junior High School, 91-16, 1990-1992 (Reel 91, Frame 647)
    - Stuttgart Public Schools, 92-64, 1992-1994 (Reel 91, Frame 675)
    - Stuttgart Public Schools, Stuttgart Junior High School, 93-15, 1992-1993 (Reel 91, Frame 707)
    - Sulphur Rock School District, Sulphur Rock High School, 93-118, 1993-1994 (Reel 91, Frame 738)
    - Swafford, Wyonne, Professional Services Agreement, 1996 (Reel 91, Frame 768)
    - Synergetics Development, Incorporated, Professional Services Agreement, 1988-1992 (Reel 91, Frame 782)
    - Synergetics Development, Incorporated, Professional Services Agreement, 1991-1993 (Reel 92, Frame 1)
    - Synergetics, Incorporated, Professional Services Agreement, 1992-1996 (Reel 92, Frame 246)
    - Teach for America, 91-145, 1991-1994 (Reel 92, Frame 322)
    - Texarkana Arkansas School District, 84-427, 1984-1986 (Reel 92, Frame 501)
    - Texarkana Arkansas School District, 88-114, 1988-1989 (Reel 92, Frame 529)
    - Texarkana Arkansas School District, 89-107, 1989-1990 (Reel 92, Frame 548)
    - Texarkana Arkansas School District, 92-28, 1992-1993 (Reel 92, Frame 568)
    - Texarkana Arkansas School District, 92-54, 1991-1994 (Reel 92, Frame 621)
    - Texarkana Arkansas School District, Fairview Elementary School, 92-76, 1992-1993 (Reel 92, Frame 673)
    - Texarkana Arkansas School District, Trice Elementary School, 92-154, 1992-1993 (Reel 92, Frame 719)
    - Texarkana Arkansas School District, Washington Intermediate School, 93-65, 1993-1994 (Reel 92, Frame 772)
    - Texarkana Arkansas School District, 95-14, 1994-1995 (Reel 92, Frame 810)
    - Texarkana Regional Arts and Humanities Council, Incorporated, TRAHC, 89-121, 1989-1992 (Reel 92, Frame 850)
    - Tri-County Community Center, Incorporated, 89-65, 1989-1990 (Reel 92, Frame 913)
    - Tri-County Community Center, Incorporated, 90-95, 1990-1991 (Reel 92, Frame 935)
    - Tri-County Community Center, Incorporated, 91-155, 1991-1993 (Reel 92, Frame 975)
    - Trumann Public Schools, 88-567, 1986 (Reel 92, Frame 997)
    - Trumann Public Schools, Cedar Park Elementary School, 95-160, 1995-1996 (Reel 92, Frame 1015)
    - Tuckerman Public Schools, 88-161, 1988-1989 (Reel 92, Frame 1075)
    - Union Medical Center, Wellness, 2nd Year, 81-254, 1982-1985 (Reel 92, Frame 1093)
    - Union Medical Center, Wellness, 81-1004, 1981-1982 (Reel 92, Frame 1114)
    - The United Methodist Church, 83-387, 1983-1984 (Reel 92, Frame 1140)
    - The United Methodist Church, Board of Global Ministries, 84-452, 1984-1985 (Reel 92, Frame 1162)
    - The United Methodist Church, Social Justice, 85-558, 1985-1987 (Reel 92, Frame 1192)
    - United Methodist Homeless Housing Mission. Incorporated, 96-4, 1995-1996 (Reel 93, Frame 1)
    - United Way of Pulaski County, Incorporated, Project Circuit Rider, Planning, 81-1006, 1981-1982 (Reel 93, Frame 88)
    - United Way of Pulaski County, Incorporated, Project Circuit Rider, 2nd Year, 81-271, 1982-1983 (Reel 93, Frame 126)
    - United Way of Pulaski County, Incorporated, Project Circuit Rider, 1st Year, 82-289, 1982-1983 (Reel 93, Frame 146)
    - United Way of Pulaski County, Incorporated, Project Circuit Rider, 2nd Year, 83-343, 1983-1985 (Reel 93, Frame 170)
    - United Way of Pulaski County, Incorporated, 84-400, 1984-1985 (Reel 93, Frame 202)
    - United Way of Union County, Incorporated, 95-181, 1995-1999 (Reel 93, Frame 246)
    - Universal Housing Development Corporation, Affordable Housing, 91-162, 1991-1997 (Reel 93, Frame 530)
    - University of Arkansas, College of Education, Sensitivity Training, Collective Bargaining with the Public Sector, 78-999, 1978 (Reel 93, Frame 700)
    - University of Arkansas, Department of Mathematics and Office of Student Affairs, Women in Math, 78-1019, 1978-1979 (Reel 93, Frame 709)
    - University of Arkansas, College of Education, Institute for Employment Relations, 79-999, 1979 (Reel 93, Frame 761)
    - University of Arkansas, College of Engineering, Minority Engineering, 80-2038, 1980 (Reel 93, Frame 769)
    - University of Arkansas, Rural Schools, 80-2039, 1980 (Reel 93, Frame 814)
    - University of Arkansas, Rural Schools, 81-256, 1981-1982 (Reel 93, Frame 833)
    - University of Arkansas, College of Engineering, Minority Engineering, 81-1007, 1981 (Reel 93, Frame 848)
    - University of Arkansas, College of Engineering, Minority Engineering, 82-286, 1982-1983 (Reel 93, Frame 902)
    - University of Arkansas, Rural Schools, 82-316, 1983-1984 (Reel 93, Frame 917)
    - University of Arkansas, Division of Agriculture, 83-361, 1983-1985 (Reel 93, Frame 941)
    - University of Arkansas, Agriculture Engineering Department, 84-458, 1984-1987 (Reel 93, Frame 993)
    - University of Arkansas, Agriculture Development, 87-767, 1987-1988 (Reel 93, Frame 1033)
    - University of Arkansas, Technology Transfer, 87-840, 1987-1988 (Reel 93, Frame 1049)
    - University of Arkansas, Farming Systems and Sustainable Agriculture, 88-56, 1988-1989 (Reel 93, Frame 1063)
    - University of Arkansas, Agriculture and Rural Policy, 88-58, 1988-1992 (Reel 93, Frame 1081)
    - University of Arkansas, Arkansas Association of Educational Administrators, AAEA, 88-155, 1988-1990 (Reel 93, Frame 1118)
    - University of Arkansas, KUAF Radio, 92-87, 1992-1994 (Reel 93, Frame 1152)
    - University of Arkansas at Fayetteville, Break the Mold, 92-172, 1992-1994 (Reel 94, Frame 1)
    - University of Arkansas at Fayetteville, Break the Mold, 93-242, Original Proposal, 1993-1998 (Reel 94, Frame 50)
    - University of Arkansas at Fayetteville, Break the Mold, Grant Agreement-Year One, 1992-1998 (Reel 94, Frame 375)
      Grant number: 93-242
    - University of Arkansas at Fayetteville, Break the Mold, 93-242, Year Two-Year Four, 1995-1997 (Reel 94, Frame 604)
    - University of Arkansas at Fayetteville, Break the Mold, 93-242, Year Five, 1997-2000 (Reel 94, Frame 838)
    - University of Arkansas at Little Rock, UALR, "Money Magic" Video Series, 78-1021, 1978-1981 (Reel 94, Frame 1075)
    - University of Arkansas at Little Rock, UALR, School of Law, Minority Scholarships, 80-2040, 1981 (Reel 95, Frame 1)
    - University of Arkansas at Little Rock, UALR, University for Youth, 82-272, 1982-1983 (Reel 95, Frame 32)
    - University of Arkansas at Little Rock, UALR, Local Government Institute, 82-284, 1982-1983 (Reel 95, Frame 122)
    - University of Arkansas at Little Rock, UALR, School of Law, Minority Scholarships, 82-288, 1982-1983 (Reel 95, Frame 182)
    - University of Arkansas at Little Rock, UALR, University for Youth, 83-329, 1983 (Reel 95, Frame 225)
    - University of Arkansas at Little Rock, UALR, Gifted Math, 83-330, 1983 (Reel 95, Frame 256)
    - University of Arkansas at Little Rock, UALR, Engineering Technology, 83-334, 1983-1984 (Reel 95, Frame 286)
    - University of Arkansas at Little Rock, UALR, Local Government Institute, 83-348, 1983-1984 (Reel 95, Frame 303)
    - University of Arkansas at Little Rock, UALR, Prehistoric Indian Rock Art, 83-350, 1983-1984 (Reel 95, Frame 324)
    - University of Arkansas at Little Rock, UALR, University for Youth, 83-354, 1983-1984 (Reel 95, Frame 343)
    - University of Arkansas at Little Rock, UALR, Arkansas Issues 1983, 83-362, 1983-1984 (Reel 95, Frame 381)
    - University of Arkansas at Little Rock, UALR, Minority Lawyers, 83-364, 1983-1984 (Reel 95, Frame 396)
    - University of Arkansas at Little Rock, UALR, Gifted Math, 83-382, 1983-1985 (Reel 95, Frame 418)
    - University of Arkansas at Little Rock, UALR, Conference on Prehistoric Indian Art, 83-384, 1984 (Reel 95, Frame 451)
    - University of Arkansas at Little Rock, UALR, International Education, 84-409, 1984-1985 (Reel 95, Frame 469)
    - University of Arkansas at Little Rock, UALR, Local Government Institute, 84-414, 1984-1986 (Reel 95, Frame 494)
    - University of Arkansas at Little Rock, UALR, Indian Rock Art, 84-419, 1984-1986 (Reel 95, Frame 529)
    - University of Arkansas at Little Rock, UALR, University for Youth, 84-428, 1984-1985 (Reel 95, Frame 557)